Mona Shamsolebad

shamsolebad.mona@gmail.com | +1 (604) 358-3457 | https://www.linkedin.com/in/mona-shamsolebad/ 202-131 20th W St., North Vancouver, BC

Summary

I started programming when I was in high school for the first time. I learned C, Pascal, Assembly and C#.net at university before I started my first real project with .Net framework. I have been a software developer for about 6 years, developing windows and web applications using .Net. After I found myself interested in mobile development, I decided to take iOS development program at college and I just finished that.

Key Skills

Hard Skills: iOS | Swift | Objective-C | C# | ASP.NET MVC | ExtJS | SQL | Familiar with Java and Android | Git Soft Skills: Happy | Reliable | Supportive | Adaptable | Collaborative

Experience

Mobile Development Student, Cornerstone College, Vancouver, BC, Canada

2019 Jan - 2019 Sep

- Worked as a team member, developing multiple projects from scratch
- · Worked individually, developing iOS apps
- · Worked as a team lead, developing a Java project
- Designed and implemented advanced algorithm problems

Software Developer, Alborz Distribution Co., Tehran, Iran 2018

Feb 2013 - Jan

- Analyzed, designed and implemented web applications using C#, ASP.NET MVC, LINQ
- · Analyzed, wrote and tuned SQL Server queries needed for reports
- Analyzed, designed and implemented Windows form applications using C#
- Defined tasks for team members using scrum methods and managing the TFS

Software Developer, Ertebatat Novin Faranam, Tehran, Iran

Mar 2011 - Jan 2013

- Designed and developed Web and Windows applications for Saderat Bank Services
- · Wrote complicated queries and functions in SQL Server
- Made reports using Microsoft reporting tools

Software Developer, System Kara Asarbakhsh, Karaj, Iran

Mar 2010 - Apr 2011

Developed web applications using C#, ASP.NET MVC and Entity Framework

Education

Cornerstone College, Vancouver, BC Mobile Development Diploma

2019 Jan - 2019 Sep

Bachelor's Degree, Shomal University, Amol (Iran)

2002 - 2008

B.S. in Computer Engineering